export const questions = [
  {
    question: "What is the primary muscle worked in a squat?",
    options: ["Quadriceps", "Hamstrings", "Calves", "Glutes"],
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Which nutrient is most important for muscle repair?",
    options: ["Carbohydrates", "Proteins", "Fats", "Vitamins"],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What does BMI stand for?",
    options: [
      "Body Mass Index",
      "Basal Metabolic Rate",
      "Body Muscle Index",
      "Basal Metabolism Indicator",
    ],
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "How many calories are approximately in one pound of fat?",
    options: ["2500", "3000", "3500", "4000"],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the recommended daily water intake?",
    options: ["2-3 cups", "4-5 cups", "8-10 cups", "10-12 cups"],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What type of exercise is running?",
    options: ["Anaerobic", "Aerobic", "Flexibility", "Balance"],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which exercise is best for targeting the abs?",
    options: ["Squats", "Deadlifts", "Plank", "Bicep curls"],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "At what heart rate is fat burning optimized?",
    options: [
      "50-60% of maximum heart rate",
      "60-70% of maximum heart rate",
      "70-80% of maximum heart rate",
      "80-90% of maximum heart rate",
    ],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the 'afterburn effect' called?",
    options: [
      "Anaerobic respiration",
      "Excess post-exercise oxygen consumption (EPOC)",
      "Lactic acid cycle",
      "Caloric surplus",
    ],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which vitamin is predominantly produced in the body by exposure to sunlight?",
    options: ["Vitamin A", "Vitamin B", "Vitamin C", "Vitamin D"],
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the process of building muscle called?",
    options: ["Catabolism", "Anabolism", "Metabolism", "Hyperplasia"],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "How often should strength training exercises be done to be effective?",
    options: ["Every day", "2-3 times a week", "Once a week", "Once a month"],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What does 'HIIT' stand for?",
    options: [
      "High-Intensity Interval Training",
      "High-Integrated Isometric Training",
      "Heavy Intensity Interval Training",
      "High-Intensity Integrated Training",
    ],
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "What should be the primary focus for weight loss?",
    options: [
      "Exercise only",
      "Diet only",
      "Combination of diet and exercise",
      "Sleep only",
    ],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which exercise does not primarily target the lower body?",
    options: ["Lunges", "Squats", "Deadlifts", "Push-ups"],
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the effect of regular physical activity on heart rate?",
    options: [
      "Increases resting heart rate",
      "Decreases resting heart rate",
      "Has no effect on heart rate",
      "Makes heart rate more irregular",
    ],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the role of electrolytes in the body?",
    options: [
      "Build muscle",
      "Provide energy",
      "Regulate nerve and muscle function",
      "Increase bone density",
    ],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which is not a macronutrient?",
    options: ["Protein", "Fat", "Fiber", "Carbohydrates"],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What type of workout involves alternating between periods of high and low intensity?",
    options: [
      "Circuit training",
      "CrossFit",
      "Interval training",
      "Endurance training",
    ],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which is not a type of stretch?",
    options: ["Dynamic", "Ballistic", "Static", "Isometric"],
    answer: 3,
  },
];